And it's a chatbot, right?
So it's very, very similar to all these other chatbots
that we have had.
But the point here is that I'm talking about the usage, right?
So the point here is that they have marketed it
as an emotionally intelligent one.
And it somehow is, right?
So when do you use pie, especially when you're dealing
with kids and children, right?
So when you want children to use AI for a very specific goal,
like learning stuff and, you know, same stuff,
it may be a very good option when it comes to children's
education, you know, or being a friend of a kid or something
like that, you know, all these emotional things
that we have.
Or when it comes to planning about your life,
or when it comes to talking about your daily stuff, you know,
they're not logical, they involve a lot of emotions, right?
So pie can be a very helpful option when it comes to those
kind of use cases.
And this is how the product was mainly marketed
and how it came up and how it popped off, right?